# LUÍS FELIPE PICARELI

# Software Developer

Highly experienced in the Games and Multimedia industry, using C#, .Net and the Unity engine. Skilled in coding a diverse range of systems, conducting thorough testing, and creating detailed documentation to achieve an effortless user experience.

## **SKILLS**

C# and .Net, JavaScript, Python, HTML, CSS, SQL, C, Java, PHP, Lua

Unity Engine, Git, Visual Studio, Linux CLI

Problem Solving, Organization, Adaptability, Attention to Detail, Creativity

English, Portuguese (Native)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Aug 2020 - Dec 2023

## **GAME DEVELOPER**

PrimeCut Games, Lisbon

- Implemented base gameplay features, such as movement and combat systems;
- Designed and developed core systems, including UI, Dialogue, Localization and Input;
- Maintained technical documentation and provided mentorship.

Nov 2016 - Aug 2018

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Addon – Digital Media, Lda, Lisbon

- Designed and developed an interactive directory for shopping centres;
- Researched and implemented systems to interact with external devices and backend;
- Prototyping innovative solutions for digital marketing.

May 2012 - Jul 2016

#### **UNITY DEVELOPER**

Universidade Lusófona, Lisbon

- Developed, and maintained a platform that used Serious Games for psychology research;
- Ported desktop applications to Android tablets to be used for cognitive training;
- Implemented Microsoft Kinect to allow physical rehabilitation in the elderly population.

#### **EDUCATION**

2014 - 2016

## MULTIMEDIA APPLICATIONS AND VIDEO GAMES

Universidade Lusófona, Lisbon

2012 - 2014

# **COMPUTER SCIENCE**

Universidade Lusófona, Lisbon

2011 - 2012

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT AND SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATION (EQF level 5)

Universidade Lusófona, Lisbon